Finishing the Game: The Search for a New Bruce Lee is
a comedy film directed by Justin Lin.
In 1973, martial arts great Bruce Lee died, his final
film, Game of Death, left unfinished.
With the public hungry for more Lee, movie execs decide to find a replacement.
This outrageous satire looks at the entire process, from the oddball candidates to
the greed and racial motivations that drive the final decision.
There's big business in the movies, and Finishing the Game
skewers it with an eye for '70s detail.
Breeze Loo, played by Roger Fan.
Tarrick Tyler, played by McCaleb Burnett.
Cole Kim, played by Sung Kang.
Troy Poon, played by Dustin Nguyễn.
Raja, played by Mousa Kraish.
Dean Silo, played by James Franco.
Finishing the Game is a 2007 mockumentary film directed by Justin Lin focusing on Bruce Lee's
final movie Game of Death (1972), which was unfinished at the time of his death.
Shot in 18 days, Finishing the Game comically satirizes the 1972 production—which used body doubles and
clips from other Lee movies—and addresses racial stereotypes in the Asian community.
Its world premiere took place at the 2007 Sundance Film
Festival, where it was an Official Selection.
It was also selected as the opening night film at the 25th San
Francisco International Asian American Film Festival.
The tone is lighthearted.